A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1990-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1990-1991
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.931
This collection consists of 20,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1993 February 11.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by John Thomas Casteen, the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1990-1991; seldom used permanent files, 1965-1992; and, adminitrative committee files, 1990-1992.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1990-1991 Boxes 1-41
SERIES II: Seldom Used Permanent Files, 1965-1992 Boxes 42-56
SERIES III: Administrative Committees Files, 1990-1992 Boxes 57-59
SERIES IV: Restricted Folders, 1990-1992 Boxes 60-61
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Files
  - "A--Al" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - "An--Az" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Administration--General 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing Services 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General (Restricted) 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Law (Restricted) 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Medical (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Applicants--General (Restricted) 1991 Fall (Box 1)
  - Admissions Applicants--Architecture (Restricted) 1990 Fall (Box 1)
  - Admission Applicants--College of Arts and Sciences (Restricted) 1991 Fall (Box 1)
  - Admissions Applicants--Darden School (Restricted) 1991 Fall (Box 1)
  - Admissions Applicants--Law School (Restricted) 1991 Fall (Box 1)
  - Admissions Applicants--Medical School (Restricted) 1991 Fall (Box 1)
  - African-American Affairs--General 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - African-American Affairs 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - African-American Affairs--Woodson Institute (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association--General--Board of Managers (3 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association of State Colleges and Universities 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association of University Professors 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reports--President's Reports 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology--General 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Applications For Position, "A-Z" (3 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Architecture--General 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Art--General 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Art--Planning and Development for the Arts 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Asian Studies--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Associated Chief Admissions Officers of Public Universities 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Associated Western Universities 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Colleges 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Universities--General (5 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities--Washington, D.C., Meeting 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Association of Governing Boards--General 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Association of Research Libraries (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Astronomy--General 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Athletics--General (4 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Athletics--Atlantic Coast Conference 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--College Football Association 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Attorney General (State) 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Auditor (Internal) General 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (State) 1990-1991 (Box 6)
  - "Ba-Bi" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - "Bl-Bp" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - "Br-Bz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Biology--General 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Business and Finance--General 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Business and Finance--General Updates (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 7)
  - Business and Finance--Planning and Budget Committee 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Ca" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Cb-Cg" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Ch" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Ci-Cl" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Coa-Com" Miscellaneous (1 of 2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - "Coa-Com" Miscellaneous (2 of 2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - "Con--Conn" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - "ConsCox" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - "Cr--Cz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Casteen--Class--General 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Casteen--General Cabinet Meetings 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Cavalier Daily 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Center for Innovative Technology 1990 Jul-Dec (Box 9)
  - Center for Innovative Technology 1991 Jan-Jun (Box 10)
  - Center for Public Service 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Charlottesville, City of [PACC] 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Chemistry--General 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - China--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Civil Rights (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Classics--General 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - College Boards--General 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - College of Arts and Sciences--General 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Commerce--General 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Community College 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Comptroller (State) 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Condolences-- "A-Z" 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Congress 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--General 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Capital (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Central Virginia 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Northern Virginia 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Tidewater 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Valley 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Consortia--Western 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Continuing Education 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Council of Presidents 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Council of Southern Universities (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - "Da-De" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - "Df-Dz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Darden School--General 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Dean's Meetings 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Development--General 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Development--General 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Development--"Perspectives" (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Development--Planned Giving Council 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Drama--General 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Education--General 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Educational Testing Service 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Engineering and Buildings (State) 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - English--General 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Enrollment--General 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Enrollment --Statistics 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Environmental Science--General 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity/AA--General 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - "Fa-Fh" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - "Fh" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - "Fl-Fz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Faculty--General 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule:General Faculty Meeting 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule:ROTC Dinner--Commissioning Speaker 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule:ROTC Commissioning 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule:Class Valediction 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Finals Weekend Schedule:Nursing Pinning Ceremony 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Food Services (Dining Services) 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - "Ga-Go" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - "Go" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - "Gr-Gz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly-General 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summaries 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - General Council--General 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - General Service (State) 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - German--General 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - Gifts and Grants--A 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - Gifts and Grants--B (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Gifts and Grants--C (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Gifts and Grants--D 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Gifts and Grants--E 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Gifts and Grants--F 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Gifts and Grants--G 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--H (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--I 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--J 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--K 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--L 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--M (1 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Gifts and Grants--M (2-3 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--N 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--O 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--P 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--Q 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--R 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--S (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Gifts and Grants--T 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants--U 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants--V 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants--W (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Gifts and Grants--X,Y,Z 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Governmental Relations 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Administration 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Governor--General 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Commerce and Resources (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Governor--Education 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Governor--Finance 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Governor--Health and Human Resources (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Governor--Natural Resources (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Governor--Transportation and Public Safety 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Governor--Washington Liaison Office (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Graduate Studies 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - "Ha-Hh" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - "Hi-Hz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Harrison Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - History--General 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Honor System/Committee General 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Housing--General 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Human Resources, Department of (effective 8/90) 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Industrial Relations (University)--General 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Information Technology (State) 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - International Students 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - International Studies 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Scholars--General 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Restoration Advisory Board--General 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Restoration Advisory Board--Committee--Newsletter (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 23)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - Law--General 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - Lawn Use Policy 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - Library--General 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - "Ma-Me" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - "Mf-Mz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Marine Science 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Mariners' Museum (1-2 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Mariners' Museum (3 of 3) 1990-1991 (Box 26)
  - Material Management (Purchasing) 1990-1991 (Box 26)
  - Mathematics--General 1990-1991 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--General (1-2 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 26)
  - Medical Center--General (3-4 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Health Sciences Council 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--Personnel (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--General 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--Personnel 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical School--General 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Medical School--Personnel (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - Music--General 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - "N-Na" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 27)
  - "Nb-Nz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 28)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges--General (3 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 28)
  - NASULGC--International Exchange Comm. 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - NASULGC--"Green Sheets" 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - NASULGC--Marine Affairs (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - National Science Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - New England Education Loan Marketing Corporation (Nellie Mae) 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - Newcomb Hall--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - "Pa-Ph" Miscellaneous--(2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - "Pi-Pz" Miscellaneous--(2 Folders) 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Parking and Transportation (State) 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Parking--General 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Personnel--General 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Personnel and Training (State) 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Philosophy--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Physical Plant--General 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Physical Plant--Project Status Reports 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Physics--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Planning--General 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Planning and Budget (State) 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Planning and Budget (University of Virginia)--General (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - President's Senior Cabinet Meetings 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Promotions (UMV)/Tenure 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Provost--General 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Psychology--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - "Ra-Rh"Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - "Ri-Rz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Real Estate Foundation--General 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Real Estate and Risk Management 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Recommendations--"A-Z" (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - Registrar--General 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - Religious Studies--General 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - ROTC--General 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - ROTC--Air Force (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - ROTC--Army 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - ROTC--Navy 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - "Sa-Sh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - "Si-Sn" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - "So" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - "Sp-Sz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - Salaries--General 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - Senate (University)--General (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - Sociology--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - South Africa--General 1990-1991 (Box 34)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - Space and Energy Management 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portuguese 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - Sponsored Programs--General 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education (4 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV)--Assessment 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - SCHEV--Commision on the University of 21st Century 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - SCHEV--Council Notes 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - SCHEV--On Line 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - SCHEV--Research Note 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - State Department of Education--General 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - State Fire Marshal (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - Student Affairs--General (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - Student Council--General 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - Summer Session--General (Empty) 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - "Tf-Tz" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 37)
  - Travel Invoices 1990-1991 (Box 37)
  - Travel Vouchers--John T. Casteen (1-3 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 37)
  - Travel Vouchers--John T. Casteen (4 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - Treasurer (State) 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - United States Savings Bonds 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - United Way/Combined Charitable Campaign 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - Universities Research Association 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - University Journal 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - University Police 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - University Press of Virginia 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - University Relations 1990-1991 (Box 39)
  - University Union 1990-1991 (Box 39)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 39)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (4 of 4) 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - "Wa-Wh" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1990-1991 (Box 41)
  - "X,Y,Z" Miscellaneous 1990-1991 (Box 41)
- SERIES II: Seldom-Used Permanent Files
  - Administrative Seminar 1987 (Box 42)
  - Administrative Seminar 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - Alumni Medical (3 folders) 1983-1990 (Box 42)
  - American Council on Education (3 folders) 1986-1991 (Box 43)
  - Associate (Provost) For Research--Classified Research 1985-1991 (Box 43)
  - Birdwood Golf Course (2 folders) 1975-1987 (Box 43)
  - Casteen--Letters of Congratulations on Presidency (4 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - Center For Public Service (3 folders) 1985-1990 (Box 45)
  - Clinch Valley College--Advisory Council 1986-1987 (Box 45)
  - Clinch Valley College--Advisory Council (1 of 4) 1965-1992 (Box 45)
  - Clinch Valley College--Advisory Council (2-4 of 4) 1965-1992 (Box 46)
  - Clinch Valley College--Moomaw Problem (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Colonade Club (3 folders) 1968-1991 (Box 47)
  - Enrollment Statistics (1 of 4) 1972-1989 (Box 47)
  - Enrollment Statistics (2-4 of 4) 1972-1989 (Box 48)
  - Faculty Retirement (2 folders) 1977-1988 (Box 48)
  - Government Office--Administration and Finance Directives 1978-1987 (Box 49)
  - Industrial Relations--Menger, Eve L. 1991-1987 (Box 49)
  - Jones, Donald 1972-1991 (Box 49)
  - Lawn Society--Prospective Member 1969-1975 (Box 49)
  - Medical Center--Replacement Hospital (1 of 3) 1984-1989 (Box 49)
  - Medical Center--Replacement Hospital (2-3 of 3) 1984-1989 (Box 50)
  - Miller Center--General (2 folders) 1989-1990 (Box 50)
  - Miller Center--Council Minutes (2 folders) 1976-1991 (Box 51)
  - Peavey, Marion B. (2 folders) 1980-1991 (Box 51)
  - Replacement Hospital Preplanning Study 1983 Jun (Box 51)
  - Physics--N.E.A.L.--Invitations to Join (2 folders) 1980-1987 (Box 52)
  - Professors Emeritus 1972-1986 (Box 52)
  - Senate (Faculty)--Leachman, Roger M. (2 folders) 1985-1989 (Box 52)
  - Senate (Faculty)--Leachman, Roger M.--II (2 folders) 1987 May-Jun (Box 53)
  - Senate (Faculty)--Leachman, Roger M.--III (2 folders) 1987 May (Box 53)
  - Use of University Property 1976-1969 (Box 54)
  - Visitors--General (1-3 of 4) 1989 Jul-1990 Apr (Box 54)
  - Visitors--General (4 of 4) 1989 Jul-1990 Apr (Box 55)
  - Visitors--General (3 folders) 1990 May-Dec (Box 55)
  - Visitors--General (3 folders) 1991 Jan-1992 Jun (Box 56)
  - Visitors--Lynn, Julie G. (student) 1990-1991 (Box 56)
  - Wilson, Jesse B. III 1984-1991 (Box 56)
  - George Washington Papers Advisory Committee 1969-1980 (Box 56)
- SERIES III: Administrative Committees
  - University Committees--General 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Athletics Advisory Council 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Calendar 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Community College 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Development Policy 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Dining Services 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Faculty Reports 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Financial Aid 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Housing 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Interests of Persons with Disabilities 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - International Students 1990-1992 (Box 57)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Judicial Policy (Restricted) 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Libraries 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Master Planning Council 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Names 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Proxy Advisory 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Radiation Safety 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Residential Life 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Scheduling 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Security and General Safety 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Traffic Appeals 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Transportation and Parking 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - Undergraduate Admissions 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - University Press of Virginia 1990-1992 (Box 58)
  - University Research Policy Advisory 1990-1992 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1990-1992 (Box 59)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1990-1992 (Box 59)
  - Women's Concerns (2 folders) 1990-1992 (Box 59)
  - Vice-President's Committees 1990-1992 (Box 59)
- SERIES IV: Restricted Folders (Box Boxes 60-61)